Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- N.Y. Medical College at Vachalla Clericals, 8/1973 (Box 57, Folder 82)
  #1792
- Presbyterian Hospital negotiation, 8/24/1973 (Box 57, Folder 83)
  #1793
- Beth Israel (Boston), Org. Comm., 8/29/1973 (Box 57, Folder 84)
  #1794
- Washington, D.C. local's delegate class, 8/1973 (Box 57, Folder 85)
  #1795
- St. Clare's Hospital Building, 8/1973 (Box 57, Folder 86)
  #1796
- Syracuse - Castle Rest Nurse Home workers portraits, 8/1973 (Box 57, Folder 87)
  #1797
- Farmworkers demo, 9/1973 (Box 57, Folder 88)
  #1798
- Paul O'Dwyer at Drug Del. Mtg., 9/1973 (Box 57, Folder 89)
  #1799
- Columbia Univ. Strike + Ratification, 9/1973 (Box 57, Folder 90)
  #1800
- Presbyterian Contract ratified, 9/1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  #1801
- Wolf Ubogy with his art show, 9/1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  #1802
- Drug Member mtg., 9/1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  #1803
- Presbyterian Social Workers (Box 58, Folder 4)
  #1804
- Fuld Hospital Strike in N.J., 9/22/1973 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  #1805
- Smithtown Nursing Home LPNs, 9/1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  #1806
- Dieticians visit Tower Suite, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  #1807
- New members class - Presbyterian, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  #1808
- Eastern L.I. RNs, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  #1809
- Richmond Memorial Strike, Oct. 1973 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  #1810
- Eastern L.I. Hosp. RNs, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  #1811
- Prof. Conference Comm., 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  #1811A
- Strong Campaign Rochester, 10/1972 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  #1812
- Hospital Strike, 11/5-11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  #1813
- Hospital Strike, 11/5-11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  #1813 (cont.)
- Hospital Strike, 11/5-11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Civil Service RXmen, 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  #1814
- Presbyterian-Arbitration of Steve Kramer case, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  #1815
- Retirees film showing, 10/1973 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  #1816
- Lab SuperMtg., 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  #1817
- Gallery 1199 Poster Show, 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  #1818
- Isabella RN-LPNs, 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  #1818A
- Ceylanese visitor, 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  #1819
- Salem (Mass.) Maint., 11/1973 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  #1820
- Ismael Santiago, Musician of Mt. Sinai (Box 58, Folder 25)
  #1822
- Drug Check off luncheon, 12/1973 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  #1823
- Fuld Hospital Strike, 12/8/1973 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  #1824
- Retirees Gym + Swim, 12/12/1973 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  #1825
- Strong memorial Hospital org. Drive, 12/18/1973 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  #1826
- Kiddie Parties, Baltimore, Philadelphia, Newark, Boston, 12/1973 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  #1827
- Farah picket, 12/1973 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  #1828
- Guild contract clinic, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  #1829
- Guild Staff, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  #1830
- Drug Del. Assoc., Nut on petitions, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  #1831
- Staff photo for election, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  #1832
- Moe Foner, Nixon enemies list, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  #1833
- Guild Anniversary Interviews, Shirley Grant, Mary Caputa, Hector Rodriguez, LaVerne DeMonde (Box 58, Folder 37)
  #1834
- Union Women's Conference, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  #1835
- Judy Berek, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  #1836
- Horace Small, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  #1837
- Rufus Baff of Bklynn Jewish, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  #1838
- Washington Ratification Nets, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  #1839
- Colorado Mtg., 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  #1840
- Wisconsin Meeting, 1/1974 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  #1841
- Blind Philly delegate (Box 58, Folder 45)
  #1842
- Kings County R. Lab Closing, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  #1843
- Butler, Pa. Members, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  #1844
- Auburn Memorial Hosp. Org. Campaign, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  #1845
- John Burnell at 1199, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  #1846
- Retirees Steve Chek + Anna Scarantino, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  #1847
- Delegate banquet, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  #1848
- Waterbury Hosp., 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  #1849
- Free First Aid Kit, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  #1850
- Seymour Posner, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  #1851
- Haiti Demo, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  #1853
- Phila. Annual Deleg. Assem., 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  #1854
- Teddy Mitchell gets award from workers at French Hosp. (Box 58, Folder 57)
  #1855
- Drug delegates awards, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 58)
  #1856
- Professional Conference, 2/1974 (Box 58, Folder 59)
  #1857
- Training Fund Grad Party, 2/28/1974 (Box 58, Folder 60)
  #1858
- 1199 Gallery: Exhibit by Tyrone Mitchell (Box 58, Folder 61)
  #1859
- King Center for Social change Mtg. to plan rally, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 62)
  #1860
- Retirees hear sex talk, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 63)
  #1861
- Ermade Maio - Speaks on Chile, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 64)
  #1862
- Congressional visits Jonathan Bingham, Liz Holtzman, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 65)
  #1863
- Chapter Mtgs., Maimonides, Bklyn Jewish, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 66)
  #1864
- Boston - University Hosp. workers Celebrate back pay, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 67)
  #1865
- St. John's pension demonstrators, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 68)
  #1866
- Swedish Ambassador: Discusses his expulsion from Chile with Hosp. Div. Deleg. Assembly, 3/1974 (Box 58, Folder 69)
  #1867
- Virginia Fields - LPN at NYU Med. Center, Finch Award recipient (Box 58, Folder 70)
  #1868
- Enid Morgan, Nurses Aide at NYU Med Center; Finch Award recipient; Grace Davidson, Supervisor, appears seated in her office, 3/1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  #1869
- Hosp. Div. Delegate's Graduating Class, Floris Saunders passes out certificate, 3/1974 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  #1870
- Eunice Allen: Deleg. Who raised money for Brotherhood Fund, 2/1974 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  #1871
- NYU Deleg. Assem. Discuss.: Doris Turner, Sam Vargas, Spkrs., 3/1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  #1872
- Jewish Home & hosp., Chapter meet, 3/1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  #1873
- Linda Harper, Pender, Delegate Jewish Home + Hosp. W. 106 St. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  #1873A
- Cong. Frank Thompson w/Godoff (Box 59, Folder 7)
  #1874
- Nat'l. Union Women's conference CLUW, 3/1974 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  #1876
- Tennis player Bill Briggs of Governeur Hosp. on job in lab + playing tennis, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  #1877
- Haitian refugee Leonce Mehu, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  #1878
- Governeur Hospital members meeting + reading 1199 News, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  #1879
- King Center for Social Change Rally to open 5th Annual Conference in NYC, 4/15/1974 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  #1880
- Cellist and union - Biologist Richard Ziegenfuss of St. Luke's on job + playing cello, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  #1881
- Lydia Amador of St. Luke's blood bank - active in Puerto Rican affairs (Box 59, Folder 14)
  #1882
- Radio Producer + Lab Tech. Chris Sheldon of St. Luke's with Margaret Dixon - Lab Tech, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  #1883
- Roosevelt Techs vote, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  #1885
- Pharmacists/passed exam, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  #1886
- Marjorie Phillips of Beth Israel, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  #1887
- Joe Dallas of Bronx-Lebanon, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  #1888
- Jim Bryant of Mt. Sinai, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  #1889
- Elone Tomkins of Mt. Sinai, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  #1890
- Max Newman of Mt. Sinai, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  #1891
- Voting for delegates at Beth Israel, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  #1892
- Edith Garcia of Beth Israel Hospital (Box 59, Folder 24)
  #1893
- Ruth Giken - opening - Gallery 1199, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  #1894
- Manhattan Eye + Ear .. Audio Legest., 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  #1895
- Miriam Fleishman of Kingsbrook, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  #1896
- Baltimore State, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  #1897
- Chas. Drew Health Center: High Noon take over of Admin. Offices to force renewal of contract talks, etc. (Box 59, Folder 29)
  #1898
- Haitian rally, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  #189
- Election Board, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  #1900
- New Jersey: Mountainside Workers - approve demands, (2) Newark votes for Local 1199 Officers, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  #1901
- Local 1199 Retirees, Mrs. Cork first St. Luke's retiree (Box 59, Folder 33)
  #1902
- 1st Philly Retiree + Pre-Retirees, Ed. Garrins, 4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  #1903
- Patricia Sears, Georgia Edwards, Earlene Walters, of Mt. Sinai Hospital (Box 59, Folder 35)
  #1904
- Jo Anne Williams of St. Mary's Home, West Hospital, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  #1905
- Org. Bell Morico + Org. Reilly? Of Comm. Staff, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  #1906
- Installation of Officers Guest Speakers, Al Heaps, Paul O'Dwyer, Paul Gibson, Amy Betances, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  #1907
- Election Board, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  #1908
- Henry Morgonthau visits 1199 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  #1909
- Harry Stoll, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  #1910
- Kingsbrook Patient - Union Committee, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  #1911
- Community RNs, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  #1912
- British Unionists visit 1199, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  #1913
- Drug Membership night, 5/22/1974 (Box 59, Folder 45)
  #1914
- 1199 P Conference, 5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  #1915
- Health Care Conference, 6/1/1974 (Box 59, Folder 47)
  #1916
- Roosevelt Hosp. - Back pay, June 1974 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  #1917
- D. Turneo getting plaque from Black Trade Unionists, June 1974 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  #1918
- Philly voting for Officers + delegates, May 1974 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  #1919
- Adelphi Workers after Hosp. closed, May 1974 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  #1920
- Bob Moore + losing Baltimore Slate, May 1974 (Box 59, Folder 52)
  #1921
- St. John's Episcopal Basketball team - Brooklyn, May 1974 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  #1922
- Holy Family, N.H. Org. Committee, May 1974 (Box 59, Folder 54)
  #1923
- Retiree's Class (Box 59, Folder 55)
  #1924
- Farm Workers at Neighborhood Maternity Center, 6/12/1974 (Box 59, Folder 56)
  #1925
- Hospital contract negotiations, Paul + Davis with press, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 57)
  #1926a
- Hospital members confront managements on contract, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 58)
  #1926b
- Drug Div. Dance, 6/22/1974 (Box 59, Folder 59)
  #1927
- AECOM demonstration, June 19, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 60)
  #1928
- RWDSU organizer, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 61)
  #1929
- Retirees film class, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 62)
  #1930
- Dell Pinckney dancer from NYU, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 63)
  #1931
- Montclair grievance, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 64)
  #1932
- Harper Strike support, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 65)
  #1933
- Retiree banquet, 6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 66)
  #1934
- Child Abuse Program, 7/10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 67)
  #1935
- Martin Goldstein, 7/12/1974 (Box 59, Folder 68)
  #1936
- Day Care, 7/24/1974 (Box 59, Folder 69)
  #1937 -- EMPTY
- Jessica Walter, 8/1/1974 (Box 59, Folder 70)
  #1938
- Jewish Memorial Grievance, 7/29/1974 (Box 59, Folder 71)
  #1939
- La Faruacia (Box 59, Folder 72)
  #1940
- B.S. Color Hosp., 8/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 73)
  #1941
- Flowers fifth voter registration, 8/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 74)
  #1942
- Flower - fifth respiratory therapists, 8/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 75)
  #1943
- Roosevelt Clericals, 8/9/1974 (Box 59, Folder 76)
  #1944
- Camp, 8/12/1974 (Box 59, Folder 77)
  #1945
- Camp Committee, 8/15/1974 (Box 59, Folder 78)
  #1946
- Phila., 1199 C Exec. Bd., 8/1974 (Box 59, Folder 79)
  #1947
- Wilmington Medical Center Org. Rally, 8/1974 (Box 59, Folder 80)
  #1948
- Latin Union Women visit, 8/1974 (Box 59, Folder 81)
  #1949
- Beakman Downtown Hospital Organizing, 8/1974 (Box 59, Folder 82)
  #1950
- Brookhaven Mem. Hosp., 8/22/1974 (Box 59, Folder 83)
  #1951
- Krupsak, 9/14/1974 (Box 59, Folder 84)
  #1952
- AECOM Meeting, 9/4/1974 (Box 59, Folder 85)
  #1953
- Einstein demonstration, 9/6/1974 (Box 59, Folder 86)
  #1954
- Krupsak Rally, 9/9/1974 (Box 59, Folder 87)
  #1955
- 1199 Boat Ride, Aug. 1974 (Box 59, Folder 88)
  #1956
- Retired memo Div. activities for 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 89)
  #1957
- Philly Delegates Sworn in 9/1974 (Box 59, Folder 90)
  #1958
- Dist. 1199 Voter Registration - Deputy Registration Sworn in.. Howard Samuels, Ramsey Clark at hosp. in Bronx, 9/1974 (Box 59, Folder 91)
  #1959
- Einstein pickets, 9/10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 92)
  #1960 -- EMPTY
- Bendimer + Sahlesinger (Box 59, Folder 93)
  #1961
- Stamford (Comm.) dietary wkrs. 1st pact. (Box 59, Folder 94)
  #1962
- new Rochelle Rally - Ossie Davis + Phil Sipser (Box 59, Folder 95)
  #1963
- R. Haye + Flower, 5th Ave. Back Pay (Box 59, Folder 96)
  #1964
- Benefit Fund move to 300 W. 43 Street - National Union Operation, 9/11/1974 (Box 59, Folder 97)
  #1965
- CLUW, 9/16/1974 (Box 59, Folder 98)
  #1966
- Retirees at orientation, 10/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 99)
  #1967
- Jubilation therapists, 10/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 100)
  #1968
- Drug Delegates, 10/7/1974 (Box 59, Folder 101)
  #1969
- Grass Restaurant, 10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 102)
  #1970
- Rochester - Strong Memorial Contract (1st) ratification, 10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 103)
  #1971
- New Jersey members portrait, 10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 104)
  #1972
- Miners Hospital, 10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 105)
  #1973
- Roosevelt X-ray Techs, 10/16/1974 (Box 59, Folder 106)
  #1974
- Principal Pharmacists, 10/23/1974 (Box 59, Folder 107)
  #1975
- Richmond Children's Center Strike, 11/2/1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  #1976
- 1199 Plaza Opening, 11/1/1974 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  #1977
- Brookdale Pharmacists, 11/1/1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  #1978
- Russian health union visitors, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  #1979
- Godoff, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  #1980
- Sherman, 11/8/1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  #1981
- Families celebrate holiday season (Box 60, Folder 7)
  #1982
- Jean Balcacer of Benefit Fund Staff (Box 60, Folder 8)
  #1983
- Nat'l. Union, Exec. Bd., 11/14/1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  #1984
- Spanish creators, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  #1985
- Sickle Cell Clinic, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  #1986
- New Drug members, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  #1987
- Principal Pharmacist's Hearing, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  #1988
- City dieticians, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  #1989
- Comm. General Hosp., pickets + meetings, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  #1990
- Beekman Hosp. contract ratification, 11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  #1991
- Baltimore - Canton Manor, Belair Conneles + Spruill family (Box 60, Folder 17)
  #1992
- HIP delegates, 12/9/1974 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  #1993
- Montefiore clerical, 12/9/1974 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  #1994
- Sleep research lab at Montefiore - Peter McGregor, Research Assist., 12/5/1974 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  #1995
- Baby Nurse Helen Brathmaite at Montefiore, 12/5/1974 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  #1996
- Retiree Crescencia Paoli, 12/6/1974 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  #1997
- Presbyterian technicians, 12/12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  #1998
- Joint Disease Clerical, 12/11/1974 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  #1999
- Ted Weiss Lectures Staff on Otis Cowcil, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  #2000
- Presbyterian Technicians, 12/13/1974 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  #2001
- Electro - encephalograph, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  #2002
- X-Mas party, N.Y., 12/15/1974 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  #2004a
- Rochester Delegate Class, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  #2005
- Julis Gogan party, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  #2006
- Drug luncheon, 12/19/1974 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  #2007
- New Jersey House - Warming - Mayor Gibson, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  #2008
- Henry Paley lectures staff on State Government, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  #2009
- Jewish Hospital in Cincinnati, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  #2010
- NYU Dietician visit, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  #2011
- King record (Box 60, Folder 36)
  #2012
- Training Fund grads + students on job + in training; NYU - S-Ray, nuclear medicine, cytotedeology; L.I.J. - hemodialysis, 1/1975 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  #2013
- Eye Care mobile van of Montefiore, 1/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  #2014
- St. Luke's Clericals, 2-4-1975 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  #2015
- West Virginia CAMC + Montefiore, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  #2016
- Park Community, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  #2017
- Eastern L.I. Hospital Strike, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  #2018
- Eastern L.I. Hospital Strike, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- Patient Care Award - 1975 (Box 60, Folder 44)
  #2019
- Drug Delegates, 2/5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 45)
  #2020
- Seymore Posner - Assemblyman in his Albany Office, 1/1975 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  #2021
- Child Care at del Assembly, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 47)
  #2022
- Presbyterian Clerical, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 48)
  #2023
- LPNs of Pond Point Home - Connecticut Arlene Crego, Roberta Rochwell, Theo Pardee, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 49)
  #2024
- Turner speaks to N.J. College Student, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 50)
  #2025
- Lab Committee hears Jeanne Stillman, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 51)
  #2026
- Presbyterian Clerical election won, 291-359, 3/4/1975 (Box 60, Folder 52)
  #2027a
- Philly-Carrie Pitts grievance in Nov. 1974/1199 News, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 53)
  #2030
- Health Comm. Jean Cook, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 54)
  #2031
- Philly Delegs. Conf. - 15 Feb. 1975 (Box 60, Folder 55)
  #2032
- Baltimore Strike of Dec. 1974, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 56)
  #2033
- Nat'l. Union founding convention, 12/1973 (Box 60, Folder 57)
  #2034
- Orange LPNs, 2/1975 (Box 60, Folder 58)
  #2035
- Jersey timecards, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 59)
  #2036
- Presbyterian technicians ratify pact., 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 60)
  #2037
- Economists (3) talk to 1199 staff, 12/1974 (Box 60, Folder 61)
  #2038
- Baltimore Deleg. Conf. -- By-Laws adopted by delegates for recon. To membership, 10/1974 (Box 60, Folder 62)
  #2039
- LPN committee, 3/111/1975 (Box 60, Folder 63)
  #2040
- Dieticians Committee, 3-12-1975 (Box 60, Folder 64)
  #2041
- Civil Service Pharmacists, 3-12-1975 (Box 60, Folder 65)
  #2042
- University of Rochester Campaign Election won, 3-6-1975 (Box 60, Folder 66)
  #2043
- Economic Conference tax workshop, 3/17/1975 (Box 60, Folder 67)
  #2044
- Murray Sharmoff, 3/1/1975 (Box 60, Folder 68)
  #2045
- Al Nash at Economic Conf., 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 69)
  #2046
- Haitian demonstration, March 18, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 70)
  #2047
- Syosset breast cancer, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 71)
  #2048
- Pharmacy Comm., 3/24/1975 (Box 60, Folder 72)
  #2050
- Winikows, 3/24/1975 (Box 60, Folder 73)
  #2051
- Salute to freedom, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 74)
  #2052
- Leon Fine, 3/27/19875, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 75)
  #2053
- Murray Sharmoff, 3/1975 (Box 60, Folder 76)
  #2054
- St. Barnabas RNs, 4/2 (Box 60, Folder 77)
  #2055
- Lab. Comm., 4/2 (Box 60, Folder 78)
  #2056
- Godoff memorial + rehearsal for dramatization, 4/1975 (Box 60, Folder 79)
  #2057
- Guild delegates class, 4/10/1975 (Box 60, Folder 80)
  #2059
- Drug Dance, 4/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 81)
  #2060
- Dorothy Abrams, 1199er, with son Mat Abrahams (Box 60, Folder 82)
  #2061a
- Barchat Memorial, 4/1975 (Box 60, Folder 83)
  #2062
- Social Service Comm., 4/15/1975 (Box 60, Folder 84)
  #2063
- Veronica Carroll, 4/1975 (Box 60, Folder 85)
  #2064
- Rosanna Lopez, 4/1975 (Box 60, Folder 86)
  #2065
- Respiratory Therapy, 4/21/1975 (Box 60, Folder 87)
  #2066
- Circus, 4/21/1973 (Box 60, Folder 88)
  #2067
- Bill Morico Comm. Org., 1973 or 1974 (Box 60, Folder 89)
  #2068
- Credit Union Couple gets loan, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 90)
  #2069
- Lab Committee, 5/8/1975 (Box 60, Folder 91)
  #2070
- Drug Delegate Assembly, 5/8/1975 (Box 60, Folder 92)
  #2071
- Papa Salrafone, 5/8/1975 (Box 60, Folder 93)
  #2072
- Kevin Doyle - Comm. Organizer, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 94)
  #2073
- Jerry Brown-Up Connecticut, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 95)
  #2074
- William Tobin early Drug member retires, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 96)
  #2075
- Thelma Bowles, 65th Birthday, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 97)
  #2076
- Kamenkowitz at LIU, 5/6/1975 (Box 60, Folder 98)
  #2077
- Drug Civil Service talks, 5/12/1975 (Box 60, Folder 99)
  #2028
- Guild delegate class, 5/12/1975 (Box 60, Folder 100)
  #2079
- Gertrude (Francis) Bullard, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 101)
  #2080a
- Louis McKnight - University Hospital - Boston - orderly - Karate expert, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 102)
  #2081
- Herman Martin of Boston, University Hospital housekeeping + jewelry maker, 5/15/1975 (Box 60, Folder 103)
  #2082
- Al Fouley - Boston - Univ. Hosp. delegate + Entrepreneur on the the side, 5/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 104)
  #2083
- Boston Jewish Memorial Hosp. member's hobby show, 5/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 105)
  #2084
- Boston Org. Ken Walden at Mass. AFL-CIO Council Meeting, 5/15/1975 (Box 60, Folder 106)
  #2085
- Boston Org. Ken Walden portrait, 5/15/1975 (Box 60, Folder 107)
  #2086
- 1199 Mass delegate class with org. Jim Bollen instructing, 5/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 108)
  #2087
- Univ. Hospital Boston members upgraded - Anthony DeSousa, Colin Graves, 5/14/1975 (Box 60, Folder 109)
  #2088
- Wesley Brown - Boston Jewish Memorial Hospital Cook, Tailor on the side, 5/15/1975 (Box 60, Folder 110)
  #2089
- Boston University Hospital member Ann Downing - Aide - at work on night shift (Box 60, Folder 111)
  #2090
- John Powell, 92 yr. old drug retiree, 5/1975 (Box 60, Folder 112)
  #2091
- National Exec. Board Meeting, 5/1975 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  #2092
- Carey demonstration, 6/3/1975 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  #2093
- Retiree's film class, 5/1975 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  #2094
- X-ray Committee, 5/1975 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  #2095
- Ann Shore, 5/1975 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  #2096
- Stuart Seltzer, June 4, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  #2097
- Bronx Maternity demonstration, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  #2098
- Conn. Dance, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  #2099
- Cabell-Huntington, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  #3000
- Nassau Joint Negotiations, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  #2101
- Turner Swearingin to City Com. On Human Rights, 4/1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  #2102a
- Hosp. Div. Deleg. Institute, 5/1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  #2103
- City Human Rights Comm. Hearing, 4/1975 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  #2104
- Drug Delegates, 6/4/1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  #2105
- Judge Bruce - Wright at June - Hospital Deleg. Assem., 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  #2106
- LPNs in Albany, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  #2107
- Gallery 1199 - Kids of Maynard - Byard and Show, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  #2108 -- EMPTY
- St. John's Retirees, 6/17/1975 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  #2109
- Spanish visitors, 6/17/1975 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  #2110
- Albany Mental Hospital, 6/19/1975 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  #2111
- Health Care Conference 'One Hospital System', 6/14/1975 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  #2112
- Central Labor Council Meet, 6/19/1975 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  #2113
- Retirees Art - 6/18/1975 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  #2114a
- 1199 P Delegate Assembly, 6/21/1975 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  #2115
- Muehlenhamp in Illinois, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  #2116
- Tom Breslin, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  #2117
- Marge Ehrlich of 1199 News at NY Labor Press Meeting, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  #2119
- Retirees banquet, 6/26/1975 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  #2120
- Barsky Medical Center, 6/25/1975 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  #2121
- Pension Dept. Staff, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  #2122
- Mental Health Sit-in, 7/8/1975 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  #2123
- Heritage Hill Home Election Victory, 6/1975 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  #2124
- Retiree Art Show, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  #2125
- Richmond Memorial Negotiation, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  #2126
- Ezratty models t-shirt, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  #2127
- Roosevelt Hosp. Demonstration, 7/10/1975 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  #2128
- Retiree Ruth Guyman doing volunteer work, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  #2129
- Orange Memorial LPNs, 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  #2130
- Roosevelt Pickets, 7/8/1975 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  #2131
- Training Fund grads William Scales and Alourde Dimetrius (Box 61, Folder 40)
  #2132
- Isabella Geraturics, 7/17/1975 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  #2133
- Camps, 7/17/1975 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  #2134
- New Jersey, St. Michael's, Chapter meeting - Ab. David Reviews Pact., 7/1975 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  #2135